This is MakeYour, one iPhone app
where GPT-5.6 creates
the tiny apps you need.
My Apps keeps every creation.
Builder is where you create
or change them.
AI Key connects your own OpenAI key
and GPT-5.6.
Together, they become one home
for your personal tiny apps.
Let's create one.
I tap New App and ask for
a daily focus checklist
with three tasks and a local reminder.
GPT-5.6 turns that prompt into
a validated, versioned app,
and MakeYour opens
the working native interface.
This is not a mockup.
I can use it immediately.
A useful app should also feel like yours.
I complete a task, return to Builder,
and ask for a calm green design
with a short evening reflection.
GPT-5.6 creates Version 3
with a new style and a new feature,
while my completed task is still there.
The app changes with me,
without starting over.
Back in My Apps, Daily Focus
is only one of many.
I can switch to a travel budget
converter,
live currency alerts,
or a private food journal.
Every tiny app can have
its own interface, capabilities, and data,
while they all live inside MakeYour.
No new Xcode project.
No separate build pipeline.
No starting from scratch.
Codex helped us build and test
the schema, validator,
safety boundary, and native SwiftUI
runtime that make this possible.
The next tiny app you need
is one prompt away.
One app.
Your tiny apps.
Make yours.