This is MakeYour, one iPhone app
where GPT-5.6 creates
the tiny apps you need.
My Apps keeps every creation.
Builder is where you create
or change them.
AI Key connects your own OpenAI key
and GPT-5.6.
Together, they become one home
for your personal tiny apps.
Now I ask GPT-5.6 for TripPilot,
a three-page travel command center with currency,
budget, itinerary, device tools, and AI.
This is the real generation run; only the
waiting time is accelerated. The first
document fails semantic validation.
Instead of timing out or asking me to
start over, MakeYour keeps my prompt,
sends precise diagnostics back to GPT-5.6
and automatically repairs revision one.
After capability review, the validated app
opens with 31 native components and 21 reviewed
capabilities. Its generated converter works too:
100 U.S. dollars becomes 3,250
Taiwan dollars. That entire interface came
from the prompt, not a hard-coded
TripPilot template.
A useful app should also feel like yours.
I complete a task, return to Builder,
and ask for a calm green design
with a short evening reflection.
GPT-5.6 creates Version 3
with a new style and a new feature,
while my completed task is still there.
The app changes with me,
without starting over.
Back in My Apps, Daily Focus
is only one of many.
I can switch to a travel budget
converter,
live currency alerts,
or a private food journal.
Every tiny app can have
its own interface, capabilities, and data,
while they all live inside MakeYour.
No new Xcode project.
No separate build pipeline.
No starting from scratch.
Codex helped us build and test
the schema, validator,
safety boundary, and native SwiftUI
runtime that make this possible.
The next tiny app you need
is one prompt away.
One app.
Your tiny apps.
Make yours.